Contact

vefgh.m.hossein@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/mohammadhossein-vefgh-20b533164 (LinkedIn)

www.sadehma.com/ (Company) barkee.ir/ (Personal)

Top Skills

Programming
Search Engine Optimization (SEO)
Web Content Writing

Mohammad Hossein Vefgh

Back End Developer at Freelance, self-employed Shīrāz

Summary

Over 8 years of extensive experience in web and client / server technologies covering all phases of project development including business requirements analysis, architecture and design, user interface design, module and component construction, testing and quality assurance, and implementation. References are available upon request.

Server Side applications developed using PHP frameworks like Laravel, Reusable Business objects Components for various industries.

Thorough knowledge of Object Oriented Analysis and Design OOAD and N - Tier Architecture

Strong in front-end GUI development using jQuery, tweenMax, Html5, CSS 3.0, etc.

Strong in backend database development including designing and administering databases, writing stored procedures, SQL and triggers for MySQL.

Develop SEO strategies and Perform site analysis, keyword research and mapping, and assess link building opportunities. Working with Docker virtualization technology, web development in the context of an isolated image container environment

Experience

Upwork

Freelance

February 2020 - Present (1 year 11 months)

Turkey

My activity is that I analyze and review the problems of web software and customers need to do back work or design the site and I accept the web software they need and if there is an agreement, I will deliver it. Most of the work I submitted was designed by Laravel Framework and PHP and the website template.

Freelance, self-employed Back End Developer 2019 - Present (2 years)

London, England Metropolitan Area

My activity is that I analyze and review the problems of web software and customers need to do back work or design the site and I accept the web software they need and if there is an agreement, I will deliver it. Most of the work I submitted was designed by Laravel Framework and PHP and the website template.

behshti company
Back End Developer
May 2019 - March 2020 (11 months)
Fars, Iran

I worked as a backend and Laravel programmer in the web basin, and the other position I held was project manager, as well as configuring my company's servers and clients, and I designed, managed, and programmed a large number of websites and software.

behashti-company Back End Developer 2018 - March 2020 (2 years) Iran

I worked as a backend and Laravel programmer in the web basin, and the other position I held was project manager, as well as configuring my company's servers and clients, and I designed, managed, and programmed a large number of websites and software.

shiraz1717 Website Manager February 2007 - February 2020 (13 years 1 month)

I worked as a web developer and back-up developer, designing and programming an online store that was a startup in the food delivery basin.

behmansh novin
Frontend Developer
January 2014 - January 2015 (1 year 1 month)
Fars, Iran

My activity in this company was active as designing front applications for Android and Java programming, and I also did PHP work with it. This company has a wide range of active mobile application design, and it was a good experience for me that the language of Android and Java I learned and implemented the template of a mobile application with XML based on my experience with HTML and CSS in this regard.

mehadresaneh Job Developer March 2012 - October 2014 (2 years 8 months) Shīrāz, Fars, Iran

My activity is that I analyze and review the problems of web software and customers need to do back work or design the site and I accept the web software they need and if there is an agreement, I will deliver it. Most of the work I delivered was designed by Laravel Framework and PHP and the website template. And the systems analysis that should be delivered in this collection.

boxoffice.ir Back End Developer September 2010 - December 2011 (1 year 4 months) Shiraz County, Fars, Iran

I started my activity by creating a PHP language design company with the help of several friends, and several projects this year, which included a store, a blog, an ad site, an SMS panel, and a site suitable for advertising. I was the main writer who was programming the front and back codes and I was working on it and it is one of my programming experiences.

Education

Shiraz University
Bachelor's degree, Information Technology